[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [3, 1, 0, 2], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": [""], "show2": [""], "showfc": [], "type": "basic", "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many surfaces are in contact with the red block?", "options": [4, 5, 1, 2], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -200, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "basic", "answer": 3, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to c1?", "options": ["N1 perpendicular up", "N1 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "basic", "answer": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to b2?", "options": ["N2 perpendicular up", "N2 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "basic", "answer": 1, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": [], "show2": [], "type": "basic", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "+N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082+20=0", "-N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": [], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: N2, 20", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "basic"}, {"question": "How many surfaces are in contact with the yellow block?", "options": [0, 1, 3, 2], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -200, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "basic", "answer": 1, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 2 due to b1?", "options": ["N2 perpendicular up", "N2 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "basic", "answer": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "type": "basic", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2082-10=0", "-N\u2082-10=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N2, ", "Downward Forces: 10", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-10=0"], "type": "basic"}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Understanding", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the dog is moving towards right with speed 5 m/s", "options": [-5, 5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": [0, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is 5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the dog is moving towards left with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": [0, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is -5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the human is moving towards right with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 0], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is -3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string if the human is moving towards left with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 0], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string is 3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in right direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [-5, 5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 5, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-3, 3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 6, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards right direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-2, 8, -8, 2], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 7, "threejssubsubstep": [3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is 2m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in right direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [5, -5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 8, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 9, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards right direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-8, -2, 2, 8], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 10, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, 5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is 5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is 8m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in left direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [-5, 5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 11, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 12, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards left direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in right direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [2, -2, -8, 8], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 13, "threejssubsubstep": [3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is -3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is -8m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of dog in left direction with speed 5 m/s", "options": [-5, 5], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 14, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": [], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the rate of change of the length of string only due to motion of human in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [3, -3], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 15, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "Net rate of change of length due to dog moving towards left direction with speed 5 m/s  and human moving in left direction with speed 3 m/s", "options": [-8, -2, 8, 2], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint Understanding", "threejssubstep": 16, "threejssubsubstep": [-3, -5], "show1": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s"], "show2": ["Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of dog is -5 m/s", "Rate of change of length of the string due tp motion of huamn is 3 m/s", "Total Rate of change of length of the string due motion of both human and dog is -2m/s"], "type": "basic", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 4, "stepQuestions": []}, {"stepName": "Final Answers", "stepNumber": 5, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What are the final accelerations, tensions and normal reactions?", "options": ["N\u2081= 20.0, N\u2082= 120.0", "N\u2081= 30.0, N\u2082= 10.0", "N\u2081= 60.0, N\u2082= 30.0", "N\u2081= 180.0, N\u2082= 30.0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "finalanswer", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-10=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1, "show2": ["Red block: +N\u2081-N\u2082-20=0", "Yellow block: +N\u2082-10=0", "Final Answers: N\u2081= 30.0, N\u2082= 10.0"]}]}]